Guide to the Army Specialized Training Division, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Army Specialized Training Program student transcripts, 1943-1945; Accession 2005-A-117
  - Silberstein Norman Ronald (Box 4, Folder 1196)
  - Simmons, Frederick William (Box 4, Folder 1197)
  - Simmons, Franklin A Jr (Box 4, Folder 1198)
  - Sims, Paul Edmond (Box 4, Folder 1199)
  - Singer, Alvin Norman (Box 4, Folder 1200)
  - Singer, Loren Adelson (Box 4, Folder 1201)
  - Siskel, Howard Benson (Box 4, Folder 1202)
  - Skelley, Joseph Francis Jr (Box 4, Folder 1203)
  - skirball, Franc (Box 4, Folder 1204)
  - Sklar, Leon (Box 4, Folder 1205)
  - Skurnick, Jack (Box 4, Folder 1206)
  - Slobodkin, Martin Harris (Box 4, Folder 1207)
  - Small, Robert Lincoln (Box 4, Folder 1208)
  - Smith, Clement Courtland Jr (Box 4, Folder 1209)
  - Smith, David Robert (Box 4, Folder 1210)
  - Smith, David Saunders (Box 4, Folder 1211)
  - Smith, Fred Cushing (Box 4, Folder 1212)
  - Smith, Harry (Box 4, Folder 1213)
  - Smith, Jack Earl (Box 4, Folder 1214)
  - Smith, Joseph Burkholder (Box 4, Folder 1215)
  - Smith, Maurice Ernest (Box 4, Folder 1216)
  - Smyth, Calvin Mason (Box 4, Folder 1217)
  - Soden, John Francis (Box 4, Folder 1218)
  - Sogg, Charles Myers (Box 4, Folder 1219)
  - Sokol, Benjamin (Box 4, Folder 1220)
  - Sokoloff, Nathan (Box 4, Folder 1221)
  - Sosnowsky, Maximo (Box 4, Folder 1222)
  - Sovich, William John (Box 4, Folder 1223)
  - Spalding, Lester Elmer Jr (Box 4, Folder 1224)
  - Sparks, John Curtis (Box 4, Folder 1225)
  - Spearen, Charles Leroy (Box 4, Folder 1226)
  - Spector, Sidney (Box 4, Folder 1227)
  - Speidel, Richard Henry (Box 4, Folder 1228)
  - Spencer, Orin George (Box 4, Folder 1229)
  - Speth, Raymon Edward (Box 4, Folder 1230)
  - Spielfogel Irving C (Box 4, Folder 1231)
  - Spillane, John William (Box 4, Folder 1232)
  - Spiller, Richard (Box 4, Folder 1233)
  - Spiner, David Ray (Box 4, Folder 1234)
  - Spitz, Arnold Inden (Box 4, Folder 1235)
  - Spoor, John Alden (Box 4, Folder 1236)
  - Sposta, Joseph William (Box 4, Folder 1237)
  - Sprenger, Claus Henry (Box 4, Folder 1238)
  - Springer, Elliott Bernard (Box 4, Folder 1239)
  - Squires, Robert Philip (Box 4, Folder 1240)
  - Stahr, Elvis J Jr (Box 4, Folder 1241)
  - Stapor, Bernard Conrad (Box 4, Folder 1242)
  - Stappenbeck Karl Emil (Box 4, Folder 1243)
  - Stark, Lewis Edward (Box 4, Folder 1244)
  - Starr, William Robert (Box 4, Folder 1245)
  - Staruski, Anthony (Box 4, Folder 1246)
  - StDenis, Gaston Pierre (Box 4, Folder 1247)
  - Stearns, William Bramhall III (Box 4, Folder 1248)
  - Steele, Donald Francis (Box 4, Folder 1249)
  - Steinberg, Leo Lee (Box 4, Folder 1250)
  - Steiner, Joseph Francis (Box 4, Folder 1251)
  - Steitz, George William (Box 4, Folder 1252)
  - Stern, Arthur (Box 4, Folder 1253)
  - Stern, Walter Jacob (Box 4, Folder 1254)
  - Stetson, Philip Ward (Box 4, Folder 1255)
  - Stevens, William A (Box 4, Folder 1256)
  - StGermain, Edwin Clarence (Box 4, Folder 1257)
  - Stiffler, George Joseph (Box 4, Folder 1258)
  - Stilwell, Roger Port (Box 4, Folder 1259)
  - Stocker, George John (Box 4, Folder 1260)
  - Stoddard, Robert Luther (Box 4, Folder 1261)
  - Stoewer, Orville Muench (Box 4, Folder 1262)
  - Stokes, Henry Duerre (Box 4, Folder 1263)
  - Stokke, Eugene Ivan (Box 4, Folder 1264)
  - Stolpa, John Thomas (Box 4, Folder 1265)
  - Stranahan, Jason George (Box 4, Folder 1266)
  - Stratigos, James Alvin (Box 4, Folder 1267)
  - Stribley, Wendell Rover (Box 4, Folder 1268)
  - Strick, Harry Walker (Box 4, Folder 1269)
  - Strong, Albert William (Box 4, Folder 1270)
  - Struble, William Thornton (Box 4, Folder 1271)
  - Stuart, Richard Kingsley (Box 4, Folder 1272)
  - Studer, John Everett (Box 4, Folder 1273)
  - Sulla, Michael Joseph (Box 4, Folder 1274)
  - Sullivan, Charles Jeremiah (Box 4, Folder 1275)
  - Sullivan, George Frederick (Box 4, Folder 1276)
  - Sullivan, James Mortimer (Box 4, Folder 1277)
  - Sullivan, William Francis Jr (Box 4, Folder 1278)
  - Sundberg, Delbert Franklin (Box 4, Folder 1279)
  - Supple, Richard Bernard (Box 4, Folder 1280)
  - Sussman, Harvey Seymour (Box 4, Folder 1281)
  - Svetic, Ralph Francis (Box 4, Folder 1282)
  - Sweeney, William Charles (Box 4, Folder 1283)
  - Swim, W B (Box 4, Folder 1284)
  - Szabo, Lester John (Box 4, Folder 1285)
  - Tabachnick Abraham Stanley (Box 4, Folder 1286)
  - Taine, Roy (Box 4, Folder 1287)
  - Talbott, Richard Nelson (Box 4, Folder 1288)
  - Talhelm, John Jacob (Box 4, Folder 1289)
  - Tannenbaum Jerome Lester (Box 4, Folder 1290)
  - Tapper, Arthur (Box 4, Folder 1291)
  - Tataranowicz Victor (Box 4, Folder 1292)
  - Taub, Marvin (Box 4, Folder 1293)
  - Taylor, John Bascom Jr (Box 4, Folder 1294)
  - Taylor, John Edward (Box 4, Folder 1295)
  - Taylor, John Edward (Box 4, Folder 1296)
  - Taylor, Walter Stark (Box 4, Folder 1297)
  - Tente, Antonio Santos (Box 4, Folder 1298)
  - Terpening, Armand Taylor (Box 4, Folder 1299)
  - Terricciano Louis Charles (Box 4, Folder 1300)
  - Tessicini, Cesioro Anthony (Box 4, Folder 1301)
  - Theil, Kenneth Warren (Box 4, Folder 1302)
  - Thomas, David Leavitt (Box 4, Folder 1303)
  - Thomas, Ellis Meron (Box 4, Folder 1304)
  - Thomas, Henry Webster Jr (Box 4, Folder 1305)
  - Thomas, Lewis Howell (Box 4, Folder 1306)
  - Thomas, Robert Irving (Box 4, Folder 1307)
  - Thompson, Jerry N (Box 4, Folder 1308)
  - Tietjen, Henry Louis (Box 4, Folder 1309)
  - Tillinghast John Avery II (Box 4, Folder 1310)
  - Timchula, Peter (Box 4, Folder 1311)
  - Tittmann, George Seibert (Box 4, Folder 1312)
  - Todd, Cletus Eugene (Box 4, Folder 1313)
  - Tolbert, Richard McDuffy (Box 4, Folder 1314)
  - Tompakov, Leonard (Box 4, Folder 1315)
  - Toplosky, Louis Joseph (Box 4, Folder 1316)
  - Torgerson, Hillard Carlyle (Box 4, Folder 1317)
  - Tow, Keith B (Box 4, Folder 1318)
  - Towle, James Ellingwood (Box 4, Folder 1319)
  - Trabulsi, Nageeb Gabriel (Box 4, Folder 1320)
  - Treuer, Robert (Box 4, Folder 1321)
  - Tripp, Granger (Box 4, Folder 1322)
  - Trostle, Charles H (Box 4, Folder 1323)
  - Turner, Julius (Box 4, Folder 1324)
  - Tymstra, Justin Cornelius (Box 4, Folder 1325)
  - Tzetzo, Perry (Box 4, Folder 1326)
  - Ugelow, Leonard (Box 4, Folder 1327)
  - Underwood, William Edward (Box 4, Folder 1328)
  - Urbancik, John Andrew (Box 4, Folder 1329)
  - Valentik, John William (Box 4, Folder 1330)
  - Valenza, Philip (Box 4, Folder 1331)
  - VanDam, Albert (Box 4, Folder 1332)
  - VanDellen, Lubbert William (Box 4, Folder 1333)
  - VanderBerg John (Box 4, Folder 1334)
  - VanDerWall August Frederick (Box 4, Folder 1335)
  - VanDusen, Roy R (Box 4, Folder 1336)
  - VanGarder, Robert George (Box 4, Folder 1337)
  - VanHoosier Charles Preston (Box 4, Folder 1338)
  - VanHouten, S Austin (Box 4, Folder 1339)
  - VanHouten, S Austin (Box 4, Folder 1340)
  - Varlan, Nicholas Peter (Box 4, Folder 1341)
  - Vars, William Courtland (Box 4, Folder 1342)
  - Vavala, Domenic (Box 4, Folder 1343)
  - Vento, Adolph Vincent (Box 4, Folder 1344)
  - VerHage, Harold (Box 4, Folder 1345)
  - Vernon, Clowers Samuel Jr (Box 4, Folder 1346)
  - Vezzani, Robert John (Box 4, Folder 1347)
  - Vierregger Raymond Edward (Box 4, Folder 1348)
  - Vincent, Irving (Box 4, Folder 1349)
  - Vittum, Bruce Farr (Box 4, Folder 1350)
  - Vogel, Robert William (Box 4, Folder 1351)
  - Voigt, George Gustave (Box 4, Folder 1352)
  - Vozel, Milan Ferdinand (Box 4, Folder 1353)
  - Wadlow, Charles Roger Jr (Box 4, Folder 1354)
  - Wagner, John Ernest (Box 4, Folder 1355)
  - Walker, Alvin Harold (Box 4, Folder 1356)
  - Walker, Charles Calvin (Box 4, Folder 1357)
  - Walker, Peter Cuyler (Box 4, Folder 1358)
  - Wallace, George Groom (Box 4, Folder 1359)
  - Wallace, Gordon (Box 4, Folder 1360)
  - Walpole, William Henry Jr (Box 4, Folder 1361)
  - Walters, Edward Lawrence (Box 4, Folder 1362)
  - Wanamaker, Ernest Aubrey (Box 4, Folder 1363)
  - Ward, Henley Irvins (Box 4, Folder 1364)
  - Ward, Herman Franklin (Box 4, Folder 1365)
  - Ward, Hugh Campbell Jr (Box 4, Folder 1366)
  - Ward, John (Box 4, Folder 1367)
  - Ward, Richard Allen (Box 4, Folder 1368)
  - Waring, John Phillip (Box 4, Folder 1369)
  - Warren, Charles Hugh (Box 4, Folder 1370)
  - Washburn, David (Box 4, Folder 1371)
  - Watanabe, Kazumi (Box 4, Folder 1372)
  - Watson, Ben Edward Mil (Box 4, Folder 1373)
  - Watson, Richard Leigh (Box 4, Folder 1374)
  - Weatherholt Kenneth Lee (Box 4, Folder 1375)
  - Webb, George (Box 4, Folder 1376)
  - Webb, John Worthing (Box 4, Folder 1377)
  - Weber, Robert (Box 4, Folder 1378)
  - Weggel, William George (Box 4, Folder 1379)
  - Weill, Ernest Alphonso Jr (Box 4, Folder 1380)
  - Wein, Eugene (Box 4, Folder 1381)
  - Weiner, William (Box 4, Folder 1382)
  - Weingast, Herbert (Box 4, Folder 1383)
  - Weininger, Arthur David (Box 4, Folder 1384)
  - Weir, Roland Lindsey (Box 4, Folder 1385)
  - Weisgerber Leonard Alfred (Box 4, Folder 1386)
  - Weiss, Barney (Box 4, Folder 1387)
  - Weiss, Louis (Box 4, Folder 1388)
  - Welsch, Frank William (Box 4, Folder 1389)
  - Wenke, Royal K (Box 4, Folder 1390)
  - Wenrich, Vernon Dale (Box 4, Folder 1391)
  - Wert, Charles Frederick (Box 4, Folder 1392)
  - West, Thomas M (Box 4, Folder 1393)
  - Westerman, Samuel Harold (Box 4, Folder 1394)
  - Westling, Ralph Ford (Box 4, Folder 1395)
  - Weston, Harold Wallace (Box 4, Folder 1396)
  - Wevers, William Garret (Box 4, Folder 1397)
  - Wexler, Eugene (Box 4, Folder 1398)
  - Wheeler, Thomas Lewie (Box 4, Folder 1399)
  - White, Philip Thomas (Box 4, Folder 1400)
  - White, William Wattles (Box 4, Folder 1401)
  - Whitfield, Edmond Elmore (Box 4, Folder 1402)
  - Whiting, David Story (Box 4, Folder 1403)
  - Whitley, Charles Orville (Box 4, Folder 1404)
  - Whitley, Richard Thomas (Box 4, Folder 1405)
  - Whittemore Charles Pearl (Box 4, Folder 1406)
  - Whitten, John Starling (Box 4, Folder 1407)
  - Whittlesey Henry C (Box 4, Folder 1408)
  - Wiesenthal Irwin Stanley (Box 4, Folder 1409)
  - Wigren, Lee Hobart (Box 4, Folder 1410)
  - Wilcox, Raymond George (Box 4, Folder 1411)
  - Williams, Carlin Reed (Box 4, Folder 1412)
  - Williams, David Morgan (Box 4, Folder 1413)
  - Williams, Manning Augustus Jr (Box 4, Folder 1414)
  - Williams, Mark Wakeman (Box 4, Folder 1415)
  - Williams, Raymond Eliot Jr (Box 4, Folder 1416)
  - Williams, Walter Piper (Box 4, Folder 1417)
  - Willis, Richard Allen (Box 4, Folder 1418)
  - Williston, Horace Jr (Box 4, Folder 1419)
  - Wilson, Elmer Leroy (Box 4, Folder 1420)
  - Wilson, James Robert (Box 4, Folder 1421)
  - Wilson, Leonard Usher (Box 4, Folder 1422)
  - Wilson, Stanley Lockwood Jr (Box 4, Folder 1423)
  - Winkler, Herman Martin (Box 4, Folder 1424)
  - Winn, Walter John (Box 4, Folder 1425)
  - Winsten, Harold Huxley (Box 4, Folder 1426)
  - Wise, Robert Belford (Box 4, Folder 1427)
  - Wisler, Orie Paul (Box 4, Folder 1428)
  - Wit, Daniel (Box 4, Folder 1429)
  - Wodka, Edward Abraham (Box 4, Folder 1430)
  - Wojcik, Casimir (Box 4, Folder 1431)
  - Wojcik, Joseph Aloysius (Box 4, Folder 1432)
  - Wolfe, Chester Harvey (Box 4, Folder 1433)
  - Wolff, Walter (Box 4, Folder 1434)
  - Wollerman, Clarence Alban (Box 4, Folder 1435)
  - Wong, Jack King (Box 4, Folder 1436)
  - Wood, James Houston (Box 4, Folder 1437)
  - Wood, John Leroy (Box 4, Folder 1438)
  - Woodhouse, Enoch Odell Jr (Box 4, Folder 1439)
  - Woods, Hugh Jean (Box 4, Folder 1440)
  - Worden, Gilbert Travis (Box 4, Folder 1441)
  - Worth, Gerald Denis (Box 4, Folder 1442)
  - Wyman, Charles Grant Jr (Box 4, Folder 1443)
  - Wymer, James Robert (Box 4, Folder 1444)
  - Wysocki, Alvin Robert (Box 4, Folder 1445)
  - Wysocki, Conrad Edward (Box 4, Folder 1446)
  - Yahnis, Christophe James (Box 4, Folder 1447)
  - Yaldizian, Gregory (Box 4, Folder 1448)
  - Yamaguchi, George (Box 4, Folder 1449)
  - Yaroch, William Carl (Box 4, Folder 1450)
  - Yatabe, Motoki (Box 4, Folder 1451)
  - Yeomans, William L (Box 4, Folder 1452)
  - Young, Harold Cope (Box 4, Folder 1453)
  - Zabik, Edward Peter (Box 4, Folder 1454)
  - Zahar, Joseph (Box 4, Folder 1455)
  - Zakrzewski Wittold Clemens (Box 4, Folder 1456)
  - Zax, Manuel (Box 4, Folder 1457)
  - Zbasnick, Henry John (Box 4, Folder 1458)
  - Zeller, Donald James (Box 4, Folder 1459)
  - Zingheim, John Julien (Box 4, Folder 1460)
  - Zlotnick, Bernard (Box 4, Folder 1461)
  - Zoghibe, James Michael (Box 4, Folder 1462)
  - Zorovich, John Raphael (Box 4, Folder 1463)
  - Zucker, Joseph (Box 4, Folder 1464)
  - Zuhusky, Joseph Albert (Box 4, Folder 1465)
  - Zukowski, Stanley Francis (Box 4, Folder 1466)
  - Zumas, Constantin Nicholas (Box 4, Folder 1467)
  - Zwick, Daniel Irving (Box 4, Folder 1468)
  - Zwirble, Constantin Stanley (Box 4, Folder 1469)
  - Zwisohn, Herman (Box 4, Folder 1470)
  - Zyzniewski Stanley John (Box 4, Folder 1471)